Student Activities Office: Subject Folders UA292 UA292
University of Rochester
- Social Behavior Board, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  This organization dealt primarily with open houses of the residence halls and the policy about co-ed hours in residence halls. Open houses were times when residence halls would allow students of the opposite sex to be in the halls and socialize with the residents.
- Social Behavior Board, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Includes policy statements from the board.
- Social Behavior Board, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Includes material on the policy of advertising alcoholic beverages on campus, in particular in newspapers.
- Songs, 1939-1950 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Includes song sheets and songbooks (University and non-University songs).
- Sororities: Alpha Sigma, 1958-1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  Includes a map to a dinner dance and sorority songs and poems.
- Sororities: Gamma Phi, 1953-1964 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Includes sorority songs.
- Sororities: Sigma Kappa Upsilon, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Contains a single packet of sorority information including songs and a brief history.
- Sororities: Theta Eta, 1958-1966 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Sororities: Theta Tau Theta, 1958-1966 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- South Asia Society, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Includes a schedule of events.
- Space Policies, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Deals with room reservations.
- Space and Usage Requests, 1958-1965 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Special Reports, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Includes a report about a pay increase for student managers of Todd Union.
- Speleology Club, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Includes information about Pennsylvania cabins, parks, and caves.
- Speleology Club Notebook, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Includes meeting minutes written into the notebook and loose sheets with cave information.
- Staff, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Contains a rough draft of a paper on the University judicial system, a staff meeting agenda, and a memo on semester goals for the office.
- Stagers, 1950-1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Includes programs and posters for many events.
- Stagers Accounts, 1956-1963 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
  Includes budget material and account ledgers.
  Arrangement
  This is a bound book of ledger sheets. Some loose documents discussing the 1963 budget have been placed in from of the book; these were originally tucked into the front cover.
- Strong Auditorium Request Forms, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Contains two forms.
- Student Activities Directory, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  Includes calendars, lists of student vendors on campus, lists of resident advisors, and the 1964/1965 directory.
- Student Activities: General, 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  Includes the 1965 Freshman Week schedule, a 1965/1966 basic dates calendar, a list of semester goals for the office, the 1965 Residence Hall Report, and floor plans for Todd Union (1964/1965), the Interpres office, Lower Strong, Upper Strong, and the second floor of a Graduate Living Center tower.
- Student Activities Office, 1934, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  Includes a filled-out questionnaire from the Association of College Unions, projected enrollments for 1965-1972, and Todd Union floor plans from 1934, 1964, and circa 1966.
- Student Activities Office: Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Student Activities Office: Weekly Calendars, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Student Activities Office: Weekly Calendars, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Student Aid, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  Contains a brochure on social security benefits for students and a press release about how much financial aid the University awards.
- Student Handbook, 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Includes the 1965 Frosh Camp Songbook, a draft of the 1964 handbook, printing cost estimates, and correspondence with other schools about sharing handbooks.
- Student Health Service, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Includes a Student Health Service brochure, information about psychiatric consultations, and emergency numbers.
- Student Orientation Program, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Contains two press releases about the summer orientation program.
- Student Peace Union, 1960-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Includes program schedules, event posters, material on the war in Vietnam, and two Sane Voice newspapers. Also includes a letter informing members of Students for a Democratic Society of upcoming events.
  Organization also used the names Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy and PEAC, and then became the Student Peace Union.
- Student Union, Planning a New, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  Includes papers from a conference for student union directors.
- Students Association, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  Contains the constitution.
- Students for a Responsible Society, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  Contains an event poster, statement of principles, and the constitution.
- Summer Orientation, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  Includes schedules, purchase orders, and material about course registration, including a booklet with course descriptions for fall 1964.
- Summer Orientation 1965: Parents (Box 21, Folder 13)
  Includes a Monroe County tourism brochure, a brochure on lilacs in Rochester, a Kodak Candid booklet, and a Memorial Art Gallery brochure.
- Summer Orientation 1965: Student Activities Office, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  Includes a Democrat and Chronicles article on summer orientation.
- Summer Orientation 1965: Students (Box 21, Folder 15)
  Includes a University handbook for undergraduate students, a Memorial Art Gallery brochure, a Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra schedule, a booklet titled Religion on Campus at the University of Rochester, and a copy of Off to College magazine.
- Summer Schedules, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  Includes room reservation forms.
- Todd Union, 1933-1964 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  Includes an activities planning guide, a 1930s-era survey of Todd Union's dining facilities, the menu from the University of Wyoming student union, and letters from alumni in the 1930s about their desire that beer not be served on campus.
- Todd Union, 1930-1965 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  Includes material about a 1965 renovation of Todd Union, statements from the depreciation account, and floor plans for the union (1959 and undated).
- Todd Union, 1929-1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Includes the student union proposal, student union constitution, Todd Union brochures, an Allegheny College grill menu, photocopies of articles in the Rochester Review from 1929/1930 and 1931, a program for a student conference titled "The Student in World Crisis," and Board of Control constitution and by-laws.
- Todd Union, 1948-1956 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Includes material on a Tabriz rug donation and maintenance.
- Todd Union, 1934-1942, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Includes reports about space usage, undated floor plans, and notes on the history of Todd Union written in 1964.
- Todd Union: Annual Reports, 1933-1965 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
- Todd Union: Building, Boards, and Activities, 1953-1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Includes papers on college union management, a University of Minnesota student center report, statistics on other colleges and their student unions, and a document titled "A Sampling of Student Unions in Region II."
- Todd Union Committee Minutes, 1937-1954 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Todd Union Material, 1954-1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Includes a questionnaire about student clubs' travel, a list of the University's students in 1962 and what organizations they took part in, photocopies of old articles, floor plans of the union with proposed changes, and a document titled "A Short History of Todd Union."
- Todd Union: Party Procedure, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Includes the Todd Union snack bar cleaning procedure.
- Todd Union: Party Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Includes event posters.
- Todd Union: Vacations and Closings, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Includes dining service schedules.
- Towers, 1962-1966 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  Includes newspaper clippings about tuition increases, Towers manuals for residents, Towers room applications, a Towers opinion questionnaire that was used to help establish policies for the buildings, and tentative floor-plans.
- Transfer Student Orientation Schedules, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- UGH!, 1955-1966 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  Includes the February 24, 1961 Campus Times.
  Organization's name stands for Under Graduate Humor magazine.
- University Enrollment Registration, 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  Includes the readmission application procedure.
- University School and Summer Session, 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  Includes an evening session brochure and editions of The Chanticleer, a University summer session newsletter.
- Usher Sign-Up Sheets, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Also includes an invitation to a theater performance.
- Varsity Press Bills Paid, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
  Contains order forms with sketches of poster requests.
- Visitation Student Unions, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Includes material on a visiting delegation to Cornell University in January 1962 to review its union. Also includes material on other unions visiting Todd Union to review its programs.
- Vocations, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  Includes a newsletter from the Syracuse University School of Social Work, a sociology booklet from the University of Rochester, and an advertisement for the University of Miami School in College Personnel Work.
- Women's Residence Hall, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  Includes Women's Residence Hall handbook.
- Women's Residence Hall, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  Includes an Anthropology 101 report titled "Coffee and Doughnuts."
- Women's Residence Hall Council, 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- World University Service Committee, 1954-1964 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  Includes event posters, donation collection procedures, and a Faculty Club menu.
- WRUR, 1960-1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Includes program schedules, a report that contains a history of the station, University policies on the station, posters for events, a 1960 report on technical problems, and a 1962 technical report.
- Yellow Key, 1938-1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Includes information on purchases of blazers with the University logo, tours given by the Yellow Keys (including tour notes and directions), and the big brother program. Also includes order receipts for yellow keys and a yellow key sketch.
  This organization was the sophomore men's honor society.
- Yellowjackets, 1958-1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Includes concert programs and a letter of recommendation to be considered for a concert tour of Europe.
- Young Democrats, 1960-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Includes event posters, ballots for officer elections, convention schedules, a letter from Robert Kennedy, and a press release about Robert Kennedy's visit to campus.
- Young Republicans, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Includes meeting posters.
- Zimbabwe African People's Union, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Oversize materials, 1926-1965 (Flatfile 1)
  Contains oversize material from the following files: Arts Committee, Bowling, Campus Times, Composite Photographs, Friends of CORE, Interpres, Outing Club: Cabin, and Outing Club: Trip to Letchworth.